https://www.phytron.eu/protection-of-data-privacy/

You are here: PhytronProtection of data privacy
Data Privacy ProtectionThank you for your interest in our website and our company! Phytron's websites contain links to other websites. Phytron is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other Web sites.Protecting the security and privacy of your personal data is important to Phytron-Elektronik GmbH. We conduct our business in compliance with applicable laws on data privacy protection and data security. In the following section you will find information on how we collect, protect and process your personal data. 1. Collection and Processing of personal dataAll site views on our website and every download of stored files is recorded. The recording is used for system optimization and statistical purposes. We record the name of the downloaded file, date and time of the site view, amount of transferred data, information on success of data transmission, web browser and the requesting domain. We also record the IP address of the requesting computer for technical reasons for about 8 weeks on our webserver. These protocols are evaluated for technical troubleshooting only. We do use this data for other purposes and we do not sell or otherwise market this data to third parties.Through our websites, Phytron will not collect any personal data about you (e.g. your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address), unless you voluntarily choose to provide us with it (e.g. by registration, survey), respectively, provide your consent, or unless otherwise permitted by applicable laws and regulations for the protection of your personal data.2. Usage and sharing of your personal dataWhen you do provide us with personal data, we use it to respond to your inquiry, process your order or provide you technical support or for technical administration.Your private data will be shared with third parties (e.g. our distributors or suppliers) in order to process your order or provide you technical support or for technical administration, only. We do not sell or otherwise market your personal data to third parties.You always have the right to withdraw from your agreement in the future. After your withdrawal from the agreement on saving your personal data, the data will be deleted as soon as it is not needed any more to accomplish the purpose it was originally recorded for or in case it is not legal to keep the recorded data. 3. Informaition on recorded dataTo receive information on what personal data is recorded please send us a written request. 4. Anonymised Website-Tracking"This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google").
Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States.
In case of activation of the IP anonymization, Google will truncate/anonymize the last octet of the IP address for Member States of the European Union as well as for other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area.
Only in exceptional cases, the full IP address is sent to and shortened by Google servers in the USA.
On behalf of the website provider Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage to the website provider.
Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.
You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. However, please note that if you do this, you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.
Furthermore you can prevent Google's collection and use of data (cookies and IP address) by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available under https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB.
Further information can be found under http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/tos.html (Google Analytics Terms of Service & Privacy).
Please note that on this website, Google Analytics code is supplemented by "gat._anonymizeIp();" to ensure an anonymized collection of IP addresses (so called IP-masking)." Data Security:To protect your personal data against accidental or unlawful destruction, loss or alteration and against unauthorized disclosure or access, Phytron -Elektronik GmbH uses technical and organizational security measures. For email traffic we cannot guarantee total data security, as the usage of emails itself is not secure.
Terms & ConditionsSitemapImprintProtection of data privacy
Company
ProfileContactsCommitmentProducts
Motors & ActuatorsDriver & ControllerMechanics & EquipmentCommunication & ProgrammingCustomised SolutionsProduct ArchiveWorld of productsIndustrialHarshExtremeSpaceSupport
Service & SupportRepairsGlossaryDownloads
